Hello my name is Mark Budnick and welcome to an introduction to my controllers and the C programming
language.
I'm a 15 year veteran in the semiconductor industry and presently serve as the computer engineering
department chair and Valparaiso University.
We have partnered with Texas Instruments to develop his hands on laboratory focused experience to take
you through a subset of our sophomore and junior level embedded systems courses step by step.
We will ask the questions students ask such as what is a my controller what is a program what is the
central processing unit What does a watchdog timer what is an interrupt what is an analog to digital
converter what is a liquid crystal display.
And finally how do we put all of this stuff together.
This course is meant for individuals who are not familiar with controllers and or the C programming
language but any experience you have will help for more knowledgeable individuals.
We believe that this course will significantly shorten your learning curve for the MSP 430 my family
throughout the course will provide scores of examples showing you how to create your own C programs
and code composer studio projects.
We work closely with Texas Instruments and elements 14 to create a laboratory kit featuring the to-I
MSP 430 as far 69 89.
Launch pad development platform with this lab kit.
We will show you how to use the most common microcontroller peripherals and provide you code to get
these peripherals up and running their course.
We use the same mixed mode format that we use in our electoral laboratories here a developer is university
and emphasis is placed on enabling students to develop their skills by continually practicing with the
tools that real developers use every day.
Short videos will kick off each of the sections followed by a step by step instructions to get you up
and running.
And if you have any questions along the way.
Our both systems team will be here to help.
That's what we're here for to make you successful.
Thanks for watching and make it a great day.